This is my assistant Rocky.
(ﾘﾀ)
これは 私の助手のロッキー｡➡
I'm Rita. Doctor Rita.
私は リタ｡ お医者さんよ｡
(ﾆｰﾅ･ﾄﾞﾗﾝｺﾞ)
あっ！ 私 またやっちゃったんだ…｡
I guess I did it again.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)あの娘の力があれば…｡
If we had that girl's power...
I believe that I told you
(ｼｬﾘｵｽ17世)
失望させるなと言ったはずだが｡
not to disappoint me.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)俺に お前の力を貸せ｡
Join forces with me!
Humans and demons...
人とか悪魔とか➡
I really don't understand.
よく分かんないな｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)くそっ 人間どもがぁ～！
Damn you filthy humans!
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)間違いありません｡
王都 アナティで➡
There can be no mistake.
Heaven
Vanaheimr
We sensed the power
in the royal capital Anatae.
あの力が使われました｡
What is the possibility that it's the child?
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)例の子供の可能性は？
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)まだ分かりませんが➡
We do not know yet.
２年前に生じた波動と
酷似しております｡
But it resembles the same surge
that we detected two years ago.
In any case,
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)とにかく
王都の捜索を強化してください｡
please intensify the search in the royal capital.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)かしこまりました｡
As you wish.
If that child is still alive,
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)
あの子供が生きているならば➡
we must find him no matter what.
必ず
見つけ出さなければなりません｡➡
To regain the faith
man once had in the gods,
人の心から消えつつある
神への信仰心｡➡
それを取り戻すには
あの子供が必要なのです｡
we will need him.
ぐっ！
我慢しなさい 悪魔でしょ？
Suck it up. You're a demon, aren't you?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
痛みに悪魔であることは関係ない｡
Demons still feel pain.
(ﾘﾀ)こんなこと続けてたら
あんた ほんとに死ぬわよ｡
You keep this up
and you really will get yourself killed.
How am I still alive?
俺は なぜ助かった？
Don't ask me.
さあね｡
((ゴロゴロ…(雷鳴)))
((ドドォーン！(雷鳴)))
まさかな｡
Unbelievable.
RAGE OF BAHAMUT
Ready!
(ﾊﾝｻ)レディー…➡
Go!
The winner is Nina Drango!
(ﾊﾝｻ)ウイナー ニーナ･ドランゴ！
ふんっ｡
That's fifteen wins in a row!
これで１５人連続勝ち｡
(男性)あぁ…｡
よ～し｡
All right.
(ﾊﾝｻ)おっ！ お次は
マッチョなにいさんクワァい？
Are you up next, Mr. Macho?
賭け金１００ルピだよ｡ クワッ｡
That's a hundred rupees to enter!
この金は 俺が頂いていくぜ｡
This money will be mine.
Best of luck to you.
(ﾊﾝｻ)そうだといいね｡
準備はいいクワァい？
レディー ゴー！
Are you all set?
Ready! Go!
ぐぐっ この…｡➡
さあさあ
お次はいないのクワァい？
Now, now, who's next?
どうなってんだ？ この女｡
What's that girl supposed to be?
Nobody likes a sore loser.
(ﾊﾝｻ)
負け犬の遠吠えは醜いですよ｡
(一同)ははははっ｡
(見物人)違ぇねぇ｡
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)今や 人間と共存する神が
お前たちだけというのは➡
It's ironic that you two are the
only gods still living among men.
皮肉なものだな｡➡
お前の相棒は
下界を満喫しているではないか｡
Your partner is fully enjoying this mortal realm.
Ready! Go!
レディー ゴー！
(男性)んん～！
ふんっ｡
(男性)うわぁ～！ 痛っ…｡
-The winner is Nina!
-Yes!
ウイナー ニーナ！
イエ～ス！
Thanks for coming!
はい ご苦労さんでした｡
ご苦労さんでした｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)はぁ…｡ 一体 なんの用だ？
What do you want?
んんっ｡ 左右で瞳の色が違う➡
Do you know of a child
with two different colored eyes?
オッドアイの子供に
心当たりはないか？
知らねぇな｡
Sure don't.
There's a high chance he's in the capital.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)王都にいる可能性が高い｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)そのガキに何がある？➡
What exactly does this brat have?
Must be a pretty big deal if you're sniffing around
down here in mortal form.
お前が人間みてぇな格好して
下界を嗅ぎ回るなんざ➡
大層なことじゃねぇか｡
You don't need to know.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)お前が知る必要はない｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)けっ！
But if you do find the child,
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)だが
もし 子供を見つけたのなら➡
Lord Gabriel would certainly consider
allowing you back into heaven.
ガブリエル様は お前たちを
神界に戻すことも考えるだろう｡
えっ！
神界を追放され➡
You must feel humiliated,
having been exiled from heaven
賞金稼ぎの元締めを
やらされるなど➡
and forced to oversee the bounty hunters.
さぞ屈辱だったのではないか？
What do you mean, exiled?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)
俺は 追放されたんじゃねぇ！➡
I left on my own, idiot!
自分から出てったんだ バカ野郎｡
Even so, this will likely be your last chance
to return to heaven.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)だとしても
お前たちにとって これが➡
神界に戻る
最後のチャンスになるだろう｡
子供を見つけしだい
私に知らせろ｡
Come tell me if you find the child.
Understood?
いいな？
≪(ﾊﾝｻ)はい それまで！
ウイナー ニーナ！
Okay, that's it! The winner is Nina!
Idiot.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)バカ野郎…｡
さあさあ お次は誰だい？➡
Now, now. Who's next?
いないのクワァい？
いないのクワァい？➡
Nobody? Nobody wants a try?
ふんっ… 情けないねぇ｡
Pathetic!
カモ～ン！
(ﾊﾝｻ)ほら➡
Come on!
Yeah, come on. Come on.
クワァモ～ン クワァモ～ン｡➡
ん？ おお～ そこのいい男！
You, there! The handsome young man!
Would you like to challenge
this superpowered young sweetheart?
このプリティーな怪力女王に
挑戦してみないクワァ？
Oh, you're running away?
(ﾊﾝｻ)
おやおや 逃げるのクワァい？
Young people these days have no can-do spirit.
最近の若い者は 骨がないねぇ｡
あっ イケメン来た｡
A handsome one indeed.
(見物人)おいおい やめとけよ｡
賭け金１００ルピだよ｡
That's a hundred rupees to enter.
おっとっと…｡
金はない｡
I have no money.
んん～？ 本物クワァい？ これ｡
Is this real?
Why are you blindfolded?
なぜ 目隠しをしている？
えっ…｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)勝負に集中するためだよ｡
さっ 腕を出して｡
It's to help her focus on the match.
Now, hold out your hand!
(ﾊﾝｻ)準備はいいクワァい？
レディー ゴー！
Are you all set?
Ready! Go!
(見物人たち)ああ～ ああ～…｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ｡➡
クワッ？ クワッ！
This guy's not bad!
こいつ やるじゃねぇか｡
おお～ すげぇ｡
Whoa, awesome!
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ～…｡
ぐわぁ～！
バキン！
クワァ～！
おりゃあ～！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ～！
クワッ！
うっ…｡
あっ ごめん！ んっ んっ…｡
I'm so sorry!
あ… あちゃ～｡
(見物人)もう一回やんのか？
(見物人)もう一回？ もう一回？
お前 何者だ？
Who are you?
I'm Nina.
私は ニーナ…｡
ニーナ！
Nina!
ドクン ドクン ドクン…(鼓動)
(見物人)誰だ？ あれ｡
(見物人)さあ？ 見たことねぇ顔だ｡
-Who was he?
-Who knows?
I've never seen him before.
クワァ？ クワッ！
(見物人)おいおい なんだよ｡
さあさあ 今日は これまでだよ｡
散った 散った！
All right, that's all for today!
Now, scram!
ふぅ～ 今日も いい稼ぎですね｡
クワッ クワッ クワッ｡
Looks like we brought in another big haul today!
In these last ten days,
(重臣)ここ１０日の間に
６軒の貴族の館➡
six aristocrats' mansions
were attacked by the rag demon.
３件の奴隷商人
悪徳商人たちの取り引きが➡
包帯悪魔に襲われ
計５６名が惨殺されております｡➡
Three slavers' and traffickers' deals too.
A total of fifty-six people have been slain.
オルレアン騎士団
漆黒兵部隊ともに➡
The Orleans Knights and the Onyx Soldiers
have failed to capture the rag demon.
討伐任務は失敗しており➡
現状 具体的な改善策は
見受けられません｡
We currently have no specific plan of action
to address this situation.
In today's war council, we will discuss
the rag demon's next possible appearance.
本日の軍議では 包帯悪魔が
次に どこに現れるかを討議し…｡
どこに現れるかなど
考える必要はない｡
There is no need to speculate
on where he will appear next.
私が指揮を執る｡
I will take command myself.
街の中央広場に悪魔を並べよ｡
その場で処刑する｡
Line up the demons in the city's central plaza.
Then execute them on the spot.
悪魔を殺し続ければ
嫌でも包帯悪魔は姿を現すだろう｡
If we continue slaughtering demons,
the rag demon will have to show himself.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)陛下 お待ちください｡
なんだ？
My Lord, please!
What is it?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)これ以上
魔の者を挑発し続けるのは➡
I oppose provoking the demons any further.
私は反対です！
ほう～｡
Captain, I don't think this is a good idea.
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)
ちょっと 団長 まずいんじゃ…｡
If we keep casually taking
the lives of demons and gods,
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)神も魔も
いたずらに命を奪い続ければ➡
いずれは力を集結し
人へと挑んでくるでしょう｡
they will eventually band together
and rise up against mankind.
それの何が問題だ？
And what about that is a problem?
挑んでくるなら
たたき潰せばいい｡
If they rise up against us,
we merely need to crush them.
しかし それでは…｡
カイザル団長｡
-But--
-Captain Kaisar.
Defend the demons too strongly
and you'll invite needless suspicion.
あまり 魔族を
かばうようなことを言うと➡
あらぬ疑いを
かけられることになるぞ｡
今宵
包帯悪魔をおびき出し 討伐する｡
Tonight we draw out the rag demon and finish him.
以前 障害となった
赤い竜も出てくるやもしれぬ｡
There is a possibility that the red dragon
that thwarted us could reappear.
邪魔するものは 皆殺しにしろ｡
Kill anything that gets in your way.
Rage of Bahamut
あ～ん｡
(ﾘﾀ)こら｡
Come on.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ヒック！ あぁ～｡
うっ うう～！
あっ そこ 気持ちいい～！
Oh, yeah! That feels so good!
You worked hard today, after all.
(ﾊﾝｻ)今日は
よく働きましたクワァらね｡
Now, I wonder if the soup is done.
(ﾘﾀ)さてと スープ出来たかな？
クワッ？ クワッ｡
That's the royal emblem.
(ﾊﾝｻ)その紋章は王家のもの｡➡
There's no way an average person
would have a real one.
そんなものを
一般人が持ち歩いてるなんて➡
It has to be fake.
まず 偽物でしょうね｡
ふ～ん｡
うわぁ～！
クワッ？
はぁ はぁ はぁ…｡
What's wrong, missy?
どうしました？ お嬢さん｡
その指輪の男のことが
気になるんですクワァ？
Are you thinking about the man
who had that ring?
I don't know! I already forgot about him!
知らない｡ 忘れた！
クワッ？
(ﾘﾀ)アザゼルと
どっちがいい男だった？
Was he more handsome than Azazel?
忘れたって言ったでしょ｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ？
I told you I've forgotten already!
(ﾘﾀ)ふっ…｡
ふん｡
You're a decade too young to be
obsessing over boys, idiot.
ケツの青いガキが
男に浮かれるなんざ➡
１０年早ぇんだよ
バカ野郎｡
さあ 食べましょ｡
Well, let's eat.
スープ これで足りるかしら？
ふふっ｡
Is this going to be enough soup?
Nina eats five people's worth.
ニーナは人の５倍は食べるからね｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)ほんとですよ｡
Isn't that the truth!
今日の稼ぎも
半分は 食事の材料代に➡
We had to spend half of our earnings today on food.
消えてしまいましたクワァらね｡
I'm starving!
おなかすいた～！
いっただっきま～す！
Let's eat!
(ﾘﾀ)いただきます｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ ﾊﾝｻ)いっただっきま～す！
-Let's eat!
ふふっ ふふふっ｡
(ﾘﾀ)ところで ニーナは なんで➡
By the way, Nina, how did you end up
living with this drunk and this duck?
この酔っ払いとアヒルと一緒に
暮らすことになったの？
I don't remember ever agreeing to it, idiot!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)俺は
許可した覚えはねぇぞ バカ野郎｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)私は
アヒルではありません｡ 神です！
And I am not a duck!
I am a god!
My teacher told me that if I went to the royal capital,
I should find someone named Bacchus
えっとね 師匠が➡
王都に行ったら
変な馬車に住んでる➡
バッカスって人を
訪ねろって言ったの｡
who lives in a weird carriage.
(ﾘﾀ)師匠？
そう 師匠が言ったの｡
-Teacher?
-Yup.
My teacher told me.
王都に来たのは初めてで
分かんないことばっかりだけど➡
It was my first time in the capital,
and there was so much I didn't know.
この馬車だけは
すぐ見つかったんだ｡
But I spotted this carriage right away.
ほんとに変な馬車だったから｡
I mean, it really was a weird carriage.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)俺の馬車を
バカにするんじゃねぇ｡
Don't make fun of my carriage.
その師匠って
一体 なんの師匠なの？
And what did this teacher of
yours teach you?
Bounty hunting.
賞金稼ぎ｡
賞金稼ぎ？
Bounty hunting?
You're a bounty hunter?
あなた 賞金稼ぎだったの？
まだ 全然 稼いでないけどね｡
I haven't collected any bounties yet though.
だって 賞金首がいないんだもん｡
でも これ見て｡
I mean, there aren't any bounties to catch.
But look at this!
(ﾘﾀ)ん？ 何？
師匠が着けてくれたの｡
What?
My teacher put it on me
賞金稼ぎの証だって｡
and said it was the mark of a
real bounty hunter.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)
そいつは偽物だ バカ野郎｡➡
That's a fake, idiot.
賞金稼ぎの腕輪は
神にしか 着けられねぇからな｡
Only a god can wear
a bounty hunter's bracer.
えっ！ ええ～ そうなの？
What, really?
My teacher is the worst.
ひどいなぁ 師匠｡
At any rate, these bracers
haven't been very useful lately.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)まあ この腕輪自体➡
あまり 役に立つことが
なくなっちまったからな｡
Thanks to that kid, Charioce,
あのシャリオスとかいう
若造のせいで➡
the rag demon is the only bounty left.
今や 賞金首も
包帯悪魔しかいなくなっちまった｡
I've basically been put out of business.
こっちも商売上がったりさ｡
And Azazel is the rag demon.
Can't really turn him in now.
包帯悪魔はアザゼルだから
今更 捕まえてもね｡
そもそも こんな若い娘に
賞金稼ぎをやらせるなんて➡
Besides, letting such a young girl
become a bounty hunter?
無責任な師匠ですね｡
What an irresponsible teacher!
勝手に俺のこと頼れだなんて
言いやがって➡
Telling her to look me up
without even asking me!
It's ridiculous!
とんでもねぇ野郎だ｡
腕輪も偽物だし ろくでなしね｡
And the bracer's a fake.
He doesn't sound very trustworthy.
確かにファバロは
ろくでなしだったなぁ｡
Yeah, Favaro wasn't exactly trustworthy.
ぶぅ～～！
クワッ!?
(ﾘﾀ ﾊﾝｻ ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ファバロ!?
-Favaro?
Damn it!
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)ああ～ くそっ！
我々オルレアン騎士団は➡
The Orleans Knights are supposed to be His Highness's
personal guard, and this is how we're treated?
陛下の近衛兵のはずなのに
この扱い…｡➡
How is this different from the rank and file?
これじゃ
雑兵と変わらないじゃないっすか｡
In any case, these are quite the forces.
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)
それにしても すごい戦力だな｡➡
It's as if we're going to war.
これでは まるで戦だ｡
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)知りませんよ そんなこと｡
それより➡
And what of it?
More importantly, where is Captain Kaisar?
カイザル団長は
どこへ行っちゃったんですか？
I haven't seen him in a while.
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)しばらく姿を見ていないな｡
Honestly.
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)
ったく… 団長がそんなことでは➡
The way the captain acted
ますます
僕らの立場は弱くなりますよ｡
only weakens our position!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ ﾊﾝｻ)がぁ～…｡
ごちそうさまでした｡
Thank you for the food!
I was certainly surprised by your appetite.
(ﾘﾀ)
あなたの食欲にも驚いたけど➡
But hearing that you knew Afro
was the biggest shock of the night.
あなたが あのアフロと
知り合いだったことが➡
今夜いちばんの衝撃だったわ｡
You know a lot about my teacher, don't you?
ねえ リタは 師匠のこと
よく知ってるんでしょ？
What was he like?
どんな人だったの？
私は 大して知らないわ｡
I didn't know him that well.
昔 ほんの少しの間
一緒に旅しただけだから｡
We only spent a little time traveling together.
ふ～ん｡
あいつのことが知りたいなら➡
If you want to learn more about him,
there's a person in the capital who could help you.
この王都に
ぴったりの人物がいるけど｡
ぴったり？ あっ もしかして➡
Really?
Do you mean an old lover?
それって恋人？
違うわね｡
No, but he certainly knows Afro
much better than I do.
でも
私なんかより アフロのこと➡
ず～っとよく知ってるんだから｡
ふ～ん｡ その人 どこにいるの？
Where can I find this person?
(ﾘﾀ)その…｡
≪(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)リタ～！
Rita!
あら｡
うっ！
There you are, Rita.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ここだったのか リタ｡
はぁ はぁ…｡
What a coincidence, Captain.
奇遇ね 団長さん｡➡
We were just talking about you.
今ちょうど
あなたのことを話してたのよ｡
ん？ ｢団長さん｣？
(ﾘﾀ)ニーナ➡
Captain?
Nina, this is Kaisar.
この人は カイザルさん｡
ロッキーのお父さんよ｡➡
He's Rocky's father.
お城で騎士をやってるの｡
He's one of the knights at the castle.
あのときは ごめんなさ～い！
I'm so sorry about then!
You're the girl with the whip.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)君は ムチ使いの…｡➡
あっ リタ
アザゼルは 今どこにいる？
Rita! Where is Azazel right now?
そんなの知らないわよ｡
Why would I know?
Do you have any idea where he might be?
どこにいるか 心当たりはないか？
If I don't do something, Azazel will be killed!
このままでは
ヤツは… アザゼルは殺される｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
お前が ほほ笑んでいるなら➡
If you keep smiling,
I just might not die tonight.
今夜
俺は死なずに済むのだろうか｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)お前は何があっても
あそこには近づくな｡➡
Whatever happens, don't go near there.
もし 俺が戻らなければ
ゾンビ女のもとへ行け｡
If I don't come back,
go to the zombie girl.
Hold on!
ちょっと！ 待ちなさ…｡
Kaisar, go stop her!
カイザル あの子 止めて！
わ… 分かった｡
Okay!
(ﾘﾀ)あんたたち 起きなさい！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ！
You two, wake up already!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)何!?
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ…｡
What?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)((今夜 陛下は
圧倒的な戦力をもって➡
Tonight, His Highness is leading an overwhelming force
to end things with the rag demon once and for all!
包帯悪魔と
決着をつけるつもりだ))
アザゼル 死んだらダメ～！
Azazel!
You can't die!
出てこい 包帯悪魔！
Show yourself, Rag Demon!
いるのだろう？
お前が出てこなければ➡
You're here, aren't you?
If you do not show yourself,
I will behead these demons one by one!
こいつらの首を
１匹ずつ はねていくぞ！
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)
ちっ！ 団長は まだなんすか？
Where is the captain?
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)静かにしろ｡
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)あっ｡ くっ…｡
Keep it down.
There! It's the rag demon!
(兵士)出た 包帯悪魔だ！
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)くっ！
We finally meet,
ようやく会えたな 包帯悪魔｡
Rag Demon!
It's okay, it's okay
I cast the usual spell
Stagnation, stagnation
My words and heart are at odds
Default
I've taken all the paint
And mixed up all the colors
Until you're left with me
So fragile
Yet strong
Close to overflowing
But not spilling
Because I'm incomplete
I won't amount to much
This is just a good luck charm
I'm not asking for your help
I was just clinging to you
Let's end it all today
I'm done living this pointless life
I've taken my last pointless breath
To whom it may concern, see ya and goodbye
I killed the person I was yesterday
A new morning is coming
What's wrong, Rag Demon?
どうした？
包帯悪魔｡
余は ここにいるぞ｡
I'm right here!
-I'm the zombie girl, Rita.
-Kaisar here!
You're so loud.
What was once my own arm is called...
Rocky?
It's not even Kaisar Lidfard.
Just Rocky!
Rocky sounds more cute.
Next time on Rage of Bahamut: Virgin Soul,
"Firestarter".
-You got a problem with that?
-No, no I don't.
Baha Baha Baha Soul
Baha Soul!!
Will you stay tuned for next time?
What is this...